<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<topic xmlns="http://www.imsglobal.org/xsd/imsccv1p1/imsdt_v1p1" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.imsglobal.org/xsd/imsccv1p1/imsdt_v1p1  http://www.imsglobal.org/profile/cc/ccv1p1/ccv1p1_imsdt_v1p1.xsd">
  <title>Discuss (U8): Hardiness Zones &amp; Micro Climate</title>
  <text texttype="text/html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Climate is important to life on earth,&lt;/strong&gt; one of the key things that we can directly see in our climate are the differences in what kinds of plants grow in different climates. Check out the link below to answer this discussion&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;&lt;a class="inline_disabled" href="https://gpsr.ars.usda.gov/phzm/vm/NC_reg_300.jpg" target="_blank"&gt;Hardiness Map - North Central United States&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When you zoom into Illinois you can see the variation of the Hardiness zones. Consult the map's color key to determine the average low temperatures&amp;nbsp; for the different colored zones throughout the state.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Notice the Micro climate (a smaller climate zone that is determined by a geologic feature) in the Chicago area.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;What are the possible causes of this micro climate?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When this updated hardiness map was released, it caused quite a stir.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Find at least one article pertaining to the updated maps and explain why you think people were concerned.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Initial posts are due on &lt;strong&gt;Wednesday by 11:59pm&lt;/strong&gt;, in which you use full sentences and proper grammar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Respond to at least two other students' posts (at a minimum), which are due on &lt;strong&gt;Sunday by 11:59pm&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be sure to respond to other students' posts with a substantive comment using full sentences and proper grammar.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</text>
</topic>
