<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<topic xmlns="http://www.imsglobal.org/xsd/imsccv1p1/imsdt_v1p1" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.imsglobal.org/xsd/imsccv1p1/imsdt_v1p1  http://www.imsglobal.org/profile/cc/ccv1p1/ccv1p1_imsdt_v1p1.xsd">
  <title>Introductions</title>
  <text texttype="text/html">&lt;h2 class="du-icon-person"&gt;Instructor Introduction&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I hope you enjoy the course and your introduction to the Earth Sciences at Dominican University. Here is a little about me:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have been teaching classes at Dominican in Earth Science, Environmental Science, Legal Reasoning, Politics, and Law. While at Dominican, I have designed courses in Earth Science, Environmental Science, and Environmental Law, as well as Environmental Politics and Legal Reasoning. I hold a JD from Thomas M. Cooley Law School, a MS in Environmental Science and Policy from University of Wisconsin - Green Bay, and a BS in Environmental Science from Saint Norbert College.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I'd like to get to know all of you as well so that I can begin to learn more about how I can serve your goals and interests.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 class="du-icon-instructions"&gt;Discussion Instructions&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please introduce yourself. Tell us something about your biography—details about your life that you would like to share.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please tell us something about what you hope to take away from this course.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;To introduce yourself, click "Reply" below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;You may write a response or...&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you wish to post a video in the discussion, watch the brief tutorial below.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class="inline_disabled" href="https://dominicanu.instructure.com/courses/324330/pages/4-dot-3-submitting-a-panopto-recording-in-a-canvas-assignment-or-discussion?module_item_id=23985812" target="_blank" data-api-endpoint="https://dominicanu.instructure.com/api/v1/courses/324330/pages/4-dot-3-submitting-a-panopto-recording-in-a-canvas-assignment-or-discussion" data-api-returntype="Page"&gt;How to submit a Video in a Canvas Assignment or Discussion&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Please feel free to respond to each other's posts as a means to begin to get to know one another.&lt;/p&gt;</text>
</topic>
