<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<topic xmlns="http://www.imsglobal.org/xsd/imsccv1p1/imsdt_v1p1" xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xsi:schemaLocation="http://www.imsglobal.org/xsd/imsccv1p1/imsdt_v1p1  http://www.imsglobal.org/profile/cc/ccv1p1/ccv1p1_imsdt_v1p1.xsd">
  <title>Discuss (U2): Rock Cycle Interactive</title>
  <text texttype="text/html">&lt;p&gt;This chapter focuses on geologic time, and the rock cycle check out this fun&amp;nbsp; &lt;strong&gt;"&lt;a class="inline_disabled" href="https://www.learner.org/series/interactive-rock-cycle/" target="_blank"&gt;Rock Cycle Interactive&lt;/a&gt;"&lt;/strong&gt; exercise for collecting rocks.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;After you have finished the exercise in collecting rocks:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Describe your childhood interactions with rocks&lt;/strong&gt;.
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Were you one of those kids who came home with rocks in your pockets? Did you have a rock collection? Did you have a favorite type of rock or mineral? Or did you interact with rocks in other ways (e.g. climbing, skipping them across the water, etc.)?&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now, think about your immediate environment or some place that you recently visited.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify the area you are thinking about&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Identify what types of rocks (sedimentary, igneous, metamorphic) you have encountered there.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Describe at least one specific rock you encountered using terms like those found on the&amp;nbsp; "Types of Rocks" screen of the exercise (e.g. crystals, fossils, gas bubbles, glassy surface, ribbonlike layers, and/or containing sand or pebbles).&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;If you don't have a particular rock in mind, go for a walk and find one, to use in responding to this part of the discussion.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Initial posts are due on &lt;strong&gt;Wednesday by 11:59pm&lt;/strong&gt;, in which you use full sentences and proper grammar.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Respond to at least two other students' posts (at a minimum), which are due on Sunday by 11:59pm.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Be sure to respond to other students' posts with a substantive comment using full sentences and proper grammar.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</text>
</topic>
